<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<month month="08">
  <day day="19">
    <link>
      <title lang="en">You Can Play The OG Diablo In Your Browser For Free Right Now</title>
      <url>https://d07riv.github.io/diabloweb/</url>
      <via>https://kotaku.com/diablo-1-browser-play-for-free-phone-blizzard-pc-1851626289</via>
      <desc>I can't claim to be able to dig out an old game save from 20 years ago but it is good fun to drop a dat file from my GoG version and see it work in a browser.</desc>
      <tags>gaming, retro, web</tags>
    </link>
    <link type="also">
      <title lang="en">Apple Podcasts Now Available on the Web</title>
      <url>https://podcasts.apple.com</url>
      <via>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/apple-podcasts-now-available-on-the-web/</via>
      <desc>Apple is venturing onto the web once again- this is particularly useful as I can now listen to podcasts on my work machines.</desc>
      <tags>apple, podcasts, web</tags>
    </link>
  </day>

  <day day="20">
    <link type="image">
      <title lang="en">The name of things you probably didn't know</title>
      <url>https://www.instagram.com/p/C9GyQlHoN0T/?igsh=MW84NmhrZ3loNTBiMQ%3D%3D</url>
      <via>https://www.swiss-miss.com/2024/08/the-name-of-things-you-probably-didnt-know.html</via>
      <image>
        <src>449753466_1144907283263610_3103874629509600075_n.jpg</src>
        <alt>A list entitled "THE NAMES OF THINGS YOU PROBABLY DIDN'T KNOW" with items such as "The space between your eyebrows is called a glabella" and "The day after tomorrow is called overmorrow".</alt>
        <copyright>2024 instagram/@englishingeneral</copyright>
      </image>
      <desc>I like these kinds of lists. Along with other people in the comments I knew aglet already from <i>Phineas and Ferb</i> but 'overmorrow' was a new one.</desc>
      <tags>language, english</tags>
    </link>
  </day>

  <day day="21">
    <link type="also">
      <title lang="en">TaskbarXI – An application written in C++ to modify the Windows 11 Taskbar</title>
      <url>https://chrisandriessen.nl/taskbarxi</url>
      <desc>Don't link to too many Windows-related things, but this is a nice way of making the Windows 11 Taskbar into a minimal dock.</desc>
      <tags>technology, windows</tags>
    </link>
  </day>
  
  <day day="23">
    <link type="also">
      <title lang="en">no hello</title>
      <url>https://nohello.net/en/</url>
      <desc>A colleague has been plagued with these recently and just so happens that this is doing the rounds again. Wish there was a non-aggressive way of sending this as a response to people who do it</desc>
      <tags>technology, work</tags>
    </link>
  </day>

  <day day="29">
    <link type="photo">
      <photo> 
        <src>r0190225.jpg</src>
        <alt>A crowd of people gathered around a singer with a microphone on a London street. Some are cheering, some are holding their mobile phones.</alt>
        <copyright>2023 Hollin Jones</copyright>
      </photo>
      <title lang="en">In Pictures: Notting Hill Carnival 2023</title>
      <url>https://londonist.com/london/art-and-photography/notting-hill-carnival-photos-2023</url>
      <desc>Londonist's photo rundown of this year's Notting Hill Carnival. Haven't been in many years but it's a great time! Music and atmosphere is like nothing else.</desc>
      <tags>event, london, uk, culture</tags>
    </link>
  </day>
</month>
