<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<month month="07">
  <day day="02">
    <link>
      <title lang="en">It's not just the fans, Samsung's chairman is also mad at the Apple-inspired designs</title>
      <url>https://www.androidauthority.com/samsung-chairman-angry-copy-apple-3467471/</url>
      <via>https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/2/24212147/samsung-chief-aint-too-happy-about-copying-apples-designs-either</via>
      <desc><i>"The internal atmosphere is currently very bad."</i> I'm all for companies copying the good ideas from each other, but the level to which Samsung copies other brands, specially Apple recently, has been pretty egregious for a long time. Wonder if this will spur a change.</desc>
      <tags>technology, apple, samsung</tags>
    </link>
  </day>
  <day day="03">
    <link>
      <title lang="en">The misleading controversy over an Olympic women's boxing match, briefly explained</title>
      <url>https://www.vox.com/sports/364856/olympics-boxing-imane-khelif-angela-carini</url>
      <desc>When terfs don't recognise a cisgender woman as a woman, it's not about "protecting women" as they say, it's about gatekeeping what one is to their narrow-minded vision of one.</desc>
      <tags>lgbtqia+, transphobia, sports</tags>
    </link>
  </day>
  <day day="06">
    <link type="also">
      <title lang="en">'Google Is a Monopolist,' Judge Rules in Landmark Antitrust Case</title>
      <url>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/08/05/technology/google-antitrust-ruling.html</url>
      <desc>This has been clear for a while, but what now? I try, <i>try</i> to use DuckDuckGo when I can but it's just not always as good.</desc>
      <tags>tech, google, internets</tags>
    </link>
  </day>
  <day day="07">
    <link>
      <title lang="en">The Circular Tube Map Is Back - New And Improved</title>
      <url>https://londonist.com/london/transport/circular-concentric-tube-map</url>
      <desc>I do love this thing. I don't agree that it's quite as practical as the designer says, I don't think it would work as a travel booklet, but printed nice and big it's really beautiful.</desc>
      <tags>london, maps, transport</tags>
    </link>
  </day>
  <day day="19">
    <link type="also">
      <title lang="en">Found</title>
      <url>https://www.smbc-comics.com/comic/found</url>
      <desc>This gave me pause</desc>
      <tags>comic, life</tags>
    </link>
  </day>
  <day day="24">
    <link>
      <title lang="en">Apple Maps on the web launches in beta</title>
      <url>https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/07/apple-maps-on-the-web-launches-in-beta/</url>
      <desc>It's been in a Safari-only beta for a little while, but seems to work in everything now. Somewhat barebones but here's hoping it'll get better.</desc>
      <tags>technology, apple, web</tags>
    </link>
  </day>
</month>
